Paul Baran Papers M1817
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- CableData Date:731016 (Container 25, Folder 11)
  WP-112: "Preliminary Concept Draft for a Request for proposal for the Arpanet," Baran & Porat
- CableData Date:731016 (Container 25, Folder 12)
  WP-111: "A Delphi Exercise Examining four Alternative Communications Policy Options," Porat
- CableData Date:731016 (Container 25, Folder 13)
  WP-110: "Using the Program Ron 1 for Cost and Value Determination", Crane
- CableData Date:731016 (Container 25, Folder 14)
  WP-109A: "Financial Analysis of the Arpanet Program (Ron1 and Ron2)", Crane
- CableData Date:731016 (Container 25, Folder 15)
  WP-108: "Arpanet Inventory", Crane
- CableData Date:731016 (Container 25, Folder 16)
  WP-116: "Independent Nodes Economics Simulation Model"
- CableData Date:731016 (Container 25, Folder 17)
  WP-115: "Independent Nodes Economics Simulation Model", Porat
- CableData Date:731016 (Container 25, Folder 18)
  WP-107: "Arpanet Inventory Listing Program (RONA)", Crane
- CableData Date:731016 (Container 25, Folder 19)
  R-117: Quart Tech Report #, "Arpanet Management Study"
- CableData Date:731109 (Container 25, Folder 20)
  S-119: "Impact of Computer networking Technology on the Dept. of Defense"
- CableData Date:731121 (Container 25, Folder 21)
  WP-120-A: "Five Questions", Baran
- CableData Date:731212 (Container 25, Folder 22)
  DP-122: "Hospitalcom: A Hospital Communications System of the Future", Baran, Parker, & Caulkins"
- CableData Date:740102 (Container 25, Folder 23)
  S-121: "Background Information"
- CableData Date:741120 (Container 25, Folder 24)
  S-117-1/M: Preliminary Draft to Collect Correction-of-Error Suggestions
- 3-Com Date:810218 (Container 28, Folder 1)
  Unanimous Written Consent of the Board of 3-Com
- 3-Com Date:810124 (Container 28, Folder 2)
  Monthly Management Memorandum (Jan, 1981)
- 3-Com Date:810228 (Container 28, Folder 3)
  Monthly Management Memorandum (Feb, 1981)
- 3-Com Date:810316 (Container 28, Folder 4)
  Publicity from Transceiver Launch
- 3-Com Date:810331 (Container 28, Folder 5)
  Appraisal of Howard Charney
- 3-Com Date:810317 (Container 28, Folder 6)
  William Krause (for COO)
- 3-Com Date:810325 (Container 28, Folder 7)
  Proposed framework for employee stock option program; Monthly Management Memo (March)
- 3-Com Date:810421 (Container 28, Folder 8)
  Board Minutes March and April, 1981
- 3-Com Date:810421 (Container 28, Folder 9)
  Salary Actions; Business Strategy Overview; Resolution for Adoption by Board
- 3-Com Date:810522 (Container 28, Folder 10)
  Results from April and May Board Meeting
- 3-Com Date:810618 (Container 28, Folder 11)
  May Results and June 22 Board Meeting
- 3-Com Date:810702 (Container 28, Folder 12)
  Letter to Holders of 3-Com Series A Preferred Stock
- 3-Com Date:810708 (Container 28, Folder 13)
  Binder to Recipients of 3-Com Corporation's 1982 Operating Plan
- 3-Com Date:810713 (Container 28, Folder 14)
  June 1981 Summary of Operations
- 3-Com Date:810728 (Container 28, Folder 15)
  July 1981 Summary of Operations
- 3-Com Date:810819 (Container 28, Folder 16)
  3-Com July Results and August 19th Board Agenda
- 3-Com Date:810911 (Container 28, Folder 17)
  August 1981 Summary of Operations
- 3-Com Date:811013 (Container 28, Folder 18)
  Incentive Stock Option Plan (ISOP)
- 3-Com Date:811112 (Container 28, Folder 19)
  October 1981 Summary of Operations
- 3-Com Date:811211 (Container 28, Folder 20)
  November 1981 Summary of Operations
- 3-Com Date:811215 (Container 28, Folder 21)
  Amendment and Restatement of Articles of Incorporation; Sale of Series B Preferred Stock
- 3-Com Date:820218 (Container 28, Folder 22)
  Board Agenda, Jan. 18, 1982; Dec. 1981 Summary of Operations
- 3-Com Date:830118 (Container 28, Folder 23)
  Board Minutes, Jan. 18, 1983
- 3-Com Date:830416 (Container 28, Folder 24)
  March 1983 Summary of Operations
- 3-Com Date:830517 (Container 28, Folder 25)
  April 1983 Summary of Operations
- 3-Com Date:830630 (Container 28, Folder 26)
  May 1983 Summary of Operations
- 3-Com Date:830713 (Container 28, Folder 27)
  June 1983 Summary of Operations
- 3-Com Date:830727 (Container 28, Folder 28)
  Agenda July 27, 1983 Board Meeting
- 3-Com Date:830811 (Container 28, Folder 29)
  July 1983 Summary of Operations
- 3-Com Date:830622 (Container 28, Folder 30)
  Binder - 1984 Operating Plan
- 3-Com Date:840117 (Container 28, Folder 31)
  Dec. 1983 Summary of Operations
- 3Com Date:790620 (Container 29, Folder 1)
  Honeywell Provides 24-hour-a-day Protection
- 3Com Date:800531 (Container 29, Folder 3)
  Deloitte Haskins + Sells, Financial Statements (Inception 6/4/79, through 5/31/80)
- 3Com Date:801001 (Container 29, Folder 5)
  Agreement between 3Com and Exxon Enterprises
- 3Com Date:820201 (Container 29, Folder 6)
  The Ether Series Book (answering questions re: 3Com)
- 3Com Date:820212 (Container 29, Folder 7)
  February, Board of Directors Meeting
- 3Com Date:820322 (Container 29, Folder 8)
  March, Board of Directors Meeting
- 3Com Date:820415 (Container 29, Folder 9)
  March, 1982, Summary of Operations
- 3Com Date:820517 (Container 29, Folder 10)
  April, 1982, Summary of Operations
- 3Com Date:820518 (Container 29, Folder 11)
  Must Win Milestones
- 3Com Date:820421 (Container 29, Folder 12)
  April, Board of Directors Meeting
- 3Com Date:820531 (Container 29, Folder 13)
  Deloitte Haskins + Sells, Financial Statements (Years Ending May 31, 1981 and 1982)
- 3Com Date:820616 (Container 29, Folder 14)
  May, 1982, Summary of Operations
- 3Com Date:820623 (Container 29, Folder 15)
  June, Board of Directors Meeting
- 3Com Date:820701 (Container 29, Folder 16)
  Local Networking of Personal Computers
- 3Com Date:820715 (Container 29, Folder 17)
  June, 1982, Summary of Operations
- 3Com Date:820722 (Container 29, Folder 18)
  July, Board of Directors Meeting
- 3Com Date:820811 (Container 29, Folder 19)
  August, Board of Directors Meeting
- 3Com Date:820901 (Container 29, Folder 20)
  3Com - "Customer and/or Investor Presentation"
- 3Com Date:820913 (Container 29, Folder 21)
  August, 1982, Summary of Operations
- 3Com Date:821015 (Container 29, Folder 22)
  September, 1982, Summary of Operations
- 3Com Date:821122 (Container 29, Folder 23)
  November, Board of Directors Meeting
- 3Com Date:830531 (Container 29, Folder 24)
  3Com - "Operating Plan"
- 3Com Date:830101 (Container 29, Folder 25)
  Controller/transceiver Board Drives Ethernet into PC Domain (Metcalfe)
- 3Com Date:840901 (Container 29, Folder 26)
  Several articles on 3Com
- Equatorial Date:770901 (Container 30, Folder 1)
  A Techno-Economic Approach to U.S. Domestic Satellite Orbit-Spectrum Regulation (Russell)
- Equatorial Date:771214 (Container 30, Folder 2)
  Application sheets on PCU's and MPB controller (Abramson)
- Equatorial Date:780801 (Container 30, Folder 3)
  Hand drawings - switching design
- Equatorial Date:780908 (Container 30, Folder 4)
  Hand drawings
- Equatorial Date:780908 (Container 30, Folder 5)
  Horley's letter confirming Tecoventure's intention to purchase 15,000 shares of Equatorial
- Equatorial Date:781120 (Container 30, Folder 6)
  Dave Baron's program (on computer)
- Equatorial Date:781130 (Container 30, Folder 7)
  Cash receipts and disbursements through Nov. 30, 1978
- Equatorial Date:781211 (Container 30, Folder 8)
  McGraw-Hill news clipping from Electronic News
- Equatorial Date:790106 (Container 30, Folder 9)
  Cryptography Design, abstract and objects (hand-written)
- Equatorial Date:790110 (Container 30, Folder 10)
  Promised information to Harvey Berke, McGraw-Hill
- Equatorial Date:790118 (Container 30, Folder 11)
  Letter to Rolf Dyce; newspaper clippings
- Equatorial Date:790121 (Container 30, Folder 12)
  Technical assessment of Equatorial Communication proposed ground station/satellite communication system
- Equatorial Date:790122 (Container 30, Folder 13)
  FCC's Data Tapes for Terrestrial Coordination
- Equatorial Date:790127 (Container 30, Folder 14)
  Letter to Harvey Berke regarding accelerating of closing
- Equatorial Date:790228 (Container 30, Folder 15)
  Equatorial Balance Sheet
- Equatorial Date:790316 (Container 30, Folder 16)
  Cost Estimate for First Phase Engineering
- Equatorial Date:790301 (Container 30, Folder 17)
  Telecommunications Rates
- Equatorial Date:790401 (Container 30, Folder 18)
  Business Plan (notebook)
- Equatorial Date:790421 (Container 30, Folder 19)
  Salary and Consulting Understanding (Parker) and other memos
- Equatorial Date:790906 (Container 30, Folder 20)
  Letters regarding financing, "Edutel's Game"
- Equatorial Date:800123 (Container 30, Folder 21)
  First Equatorial Board Meeting
- Equatorial Date:800303 (Container 30, Folder 22)
  Receipt for Stock Certificate #A-17 (90,195 shares, preferred) and for #14 (old Equatorial Communications Co. ) common stock
- Equatorial Date:801014 (Container 30, Folder 23)
  Patent Application - Satellite Communications System and Apparatus
- Equatorial Date:810121 (Container 30, Folder 24)
  Formal drawings for Patent Application for Satellite Communication System and apparatus
- Equatorial Date:820101 (Container 30, Folder 25)
  Clippings, 1982
- Equatorial Date:840720 (Container 30, Folder 26)
  Copy of Patent (Parker) and other letters and memos
- Equatorial Date:850101 (Container 30, Folder 27)
  Clippings, 1985
- Equatorial Date:850609 (Container 30, Folder 28)
  Complaint of Patent Infringement (Townsend & Townsend and Wilson, Sonsini)
- Equatorial Date:851120 (Container 30, Folder 29)
  Letter from Gallagher regarding Patent infringement (file EQT-0300RE)
- Equatorial Date:870601 (Container 30, Folder 30)
  Clippings, 1987
- Equatorial Date:880118 (Container 30, Folder 31)
  Reissue Patent Application: Satellite Communications System and Apparatus (Gallaher)
- Equatorial Date:881118 (Container 30, Folder 32)
- Equatorial Date:880127 (Container 30, Folder 33)
  PB's reply (in jest) to Gallagher
- Packetcable,Board Date:821207 (Container 34, Folder 1)
  Board of Directors Meeting, Dec. 7, 1982 (folder)
- Packetcable,Board Date:820601 (Container 34, Folder 2)
  Business Plan, June 1982
- Packetcable,Board Date:830801 (Container 34, Folder 3)
  Operating Plan, Aug. 1, 1983
- Packetcable,Board Date:831205 (Container 34, Folder 4)
  Letter to Board from PB
- Packetcable,Board Date:840104 (Container 34, Folder 5)
  Board of Directors Meeting, Jan. 4, 1984
- Packetcable,Board Date:840213 (Container 34, Folder 6)
  PacketCable in the Netherlands (and other info)
- Packetcable,Board Date:840214 (Container 34, Folder 7)
  Board of Directors Meeting, Feb. 14, 1984
- Packetcable,Board Date:840410 (Container 34, Folder 8)
  Board of Directors Meeting, April 10, 1984
- Packetcable,Board Date:840515 (Container 34, Folder 9)
  Board of Directors Meeting, May 15, 1984
- Packetcable,Board Date:840630 (Container 34, Folder 10)
  Business Plan, July 1, 1984 through June 30, 1984
- Packetcable,Board Date:850222 (Container 34, Folder 11)
  Stock Increase Recommendations
- Packetcable,Board Date:850304 (Container 34, Folder 12)
  Board of Directors Meeting, March 12, 1985
- Packetcable,Board Date:850415 (Container 34, Folder 13)
  Board of Directors Meeting, April 15, 1985
- Packetcable,Board Date:850513 (Container 34, Folder 14)
  Board of Directors Meeting, May 13, 1985
- Packetcable,Board Date:850620 (Container 34, Folder 15)
  Board of Directors Meeting, June 20, 1985
- Packetcable,Board Date:850627 (Container 34, Folder 16)
  Board of Directors Meeting, June 27, 1985
- Packetcable,Board Date:850725 (Container 34, Folder 17)
  Board of Directors Meeting, July 25, 1985
- Packetcable,Board Date:850903 (Container 34, Folder 18)
  Board of Directors Minutes, Nov. 8, 1985 (folder)
- Packetcable,Board Date:851210 (Container 34, Folder 19)
  Notice of Special Board Meeting, Dec. 13, 1985 (folder)
- Packetcable,Board Date:860102 (Container 34, Folder 20)
  Notice of Special Board Meeting, Jan. 8, 1986 (folder)
- Packetcable,Board Date:830901 (Container 35, Folder 1)
  Financial Statements, 3 months, ending Sept. 1983 (folder)
- Packetcable,Board Date:830725 (Container 35, Folder 2)
  Board of Directors Meeting, July 25, 1983
- Packetcable,Board Date:830831 (Container 35, Folder 3)
  Board of Directors Meeting, Aug. 31, 1983
- Packetcable,Board Date:830916 (Container 35, Folder 4)
  Board of Directors Meeting, Sept. 16, 1983
- Packetcable,Board Date:830901 (Container 35, Folder 5)
  Standard Oil Presentation, Sept, 1983
- Packetcable,Board Date:831017 (Container 35, Folder 6)
  Board of Directors Meeting, Oct. 17, 1983
- Packetcable,Board Date:840109 (Container 35, Folder 7)
  Status of President Search for PacketCable; "Funding of High Technology Ventures" (folder)
- Packetcable,Board Date:840112 (Container 35, Folder 8)
  Financial Report, 6 months ending Dec. 31, 1983 (folder)
- Packetcable,Board Date:840613 (Container 35, Folder 9)
  Board of Directors Meeting, June 19, 1984 (folder)
- Packetcable,Board Date:840810 (Container 35, Folder 10)
  Board of Directors Meeting, Aug. 10, 1984
- Packetcable,Board Date:841003 (Container 35, Folder 11)
  Board of Directors Meeting, Oct. 3, 1984
- Packetcable,Board Date:841113 (Container 35, Folder 12)
  Board of Directors Meeting, Nov. 13, 1984
- Packetcable,Board Date:841211 (Container 35, Folder 13)
  Board of Directors Meeting, Dec. 11, 1984
- Packetcable,Board Date:850104 (Container 35, Folder 14)
  Board of Directors Meeting, Jan. 4, 1985
- Packetcable,Board Date:850211 (Container 35, Folder 15)
  Board of Directors Meeting, Feb. 11, 1985
- Packetcable,Board Date:850806 (Container 35, Folder 16)
  Board of Directors Meeting, Aug. 6 & 7, 1985; Sept. 3, 1985; 401K Program (folder)
- Packetcable,Board Date:850913 (Container 35, Folder 17)
  Board of Directors Meeting, Sept. 13, 1985 (folder)
- Packetcable,Board Date:850925 (Container 35, Folder 18)
  Board of Directors Meeting, Sept. 25, 1985 (folder)
- Packetcable,Board Date:851018 (Container 35, Folder 19)
  Board of Directors Meeting, Oct. 18, 1985
- Packetcable & Tech Date:801001 (Container 36, Folder 1)
  Working Books, Background Reading, "Nature of Business Interest"
- Packetcable & Tech Date:801015 (Container 36, Folder 2)
  Working Books, Background Reading, "Evolution"
- Packetcable & Tech Date:801015 (Container 36, Folder 3)
  Working Books, Background Reading, "Present Products & Status"
- Packetcable & Tech Date:810301 (Container 36, Folder 4)
  STU Description/Spec Draft
- Packetcable & Tech Date:810320 (Container 36, Folder 5)
  Minimum Head-End Computer for 10,000 Subscribers
- Packetcable & Tech Date:810406 (Container 36, Folder 6)
  Some Thoughts on Specifications
- Packetcable & Tech Date:810406 (Container 36, Folder 7)
  Cable A/B Redundancy; Packaging STEs
- Packetcable & Tech Date:810406 (Container 36, Folder 8)
  Contract for Research & Development, Schedule A - Overall Research Objectives
- Packetcable & Tech Date:810407 (Container 36, Folder 9)
  Modular Development of PacketCable Services 36 10 810414 Packetcable & Tech PacketCable's Objectives - Status and Technology Development"
- Packetcable & Tech Date:840330 (Container 36, Folder 11)
  Working Books, "Computer Configuration & Software Tools"
- Packetcable & Tech Date:840630 (Container 36, Folder 12)
  Working Books, April to June, 1984
- Packetcable & Tech Date:850515 (Container 36, Folder 13)
  Working Books, "Investor Background Tutorial Presentation"
- Packetcable & Tech Date:850515 (Container 36, Folder 14)
  Working Books, "Update to Descriptive Memorandum dated Oct. 1984"
- Packetcable Date:840731 (Container 37, Folder 1)
  Working Books, July, 1984
- Packetcable Date:840801 (Container 37, Folder 2)
  Working Books, Aug. to Sept, 1984
- Packetcable Date:841001 (Container 37, Folder 3)
  Working Books, Oct. to Dec, 1984
- Packetcable Date:850101 (Container 37, Folder 4)
  Working Books, Jan. to March, 1985
- Packetcable Date:850401 (Container 37, Folder 5)
  Working Books, Apr. to June, 1985
- Packetcable Date:850601 (Container 37, Folder 6)
  Working Books, June to Dec, 1985
- Pac.Tech/Amoco Date:830401 (Container 39, Folder 1)
- Pac.Tech/Amoco Date:830830 (Container 39, Folder 2)
  Amoco Fun and Games, Standard Oil visitors meeting (folder)
- Pac.Tech/Amoco Date:831010 (Container 39, Folder 3)
  Amoco Fun and Games, Correspondence re: next round of equity financing & Standard's participation (folder)
- Pac.Tech/Amoco Date:840316 (Container 39, Folder 4)
  Amoco Fun and Games, 1984-85 (red binder)
- Pac.Tech/Amoco Date:850801 (Container 39, Folder 5)
  Amoco Fun and Games, 1985 (red binder)
- Pac.Tech/Amoco Date:851107 (Container 39, Folder 6)
  Amoco Fun and Games, Amoco correspondence (folder)
- Pac.Tech/Amoco Date:860101 (Container 39, Folder 7)
  Amoco Fun and Games, 1986 Partnership Report (red binder)
- Pac.Tech/Amoco Date:860519 (Container 39, Folder 8)
  Amoco Fun and Games, March, 1986 - Sept. 20, 1985 (red binder)
- Pac.Tech/Amoco Date:861016 (Container 39, Folder 9)
  Amoco Fun and Games, 1985-86 (red binder)
- PB Papers 1972-1973 Box 1 (Container 40)
  next box is B-63
- PacketCable & Tech Date:801201 (Container 43, Folder 1)
  Interactive Cable Investors: Exhibit A - Limited Partnership Agreement
- PacketCable & Tech Date:801217 (Container 43, Folder 2)
  A California Limited Partnership (to be informed); 100 Limited Partnership Interests at $5,000 per unit
- PacketCable & Tech Date:810715 (Container 43, Folder 3)
  Inquiry Prior to Initial Investments
- PacketCable & Tech Date:810813 (Container 43, Folder 4)
  Final Report to Interactive Cable Investors
- PacketCable & Tech Date:820820 (Container 43, Folder 5)
  Blyth Eastman Paine Webber's recommendations for private placement of equity for PacketCable
- PacketCable & Tech Date:821025 (Container 43, Folder 6)
  Copy of PacketCable Non-disclosure Agreement
- PacketCable & Tech Date:830101 (Container 43, Folder 7)
  1983 Stock Option Plan
- PacketCable & Tech Date:830211 (Container 43, Folder 8)
  Letter to Wm. Bryant, Standard Oil, re: request for additional information on PacketCable
- PacketCable & Tech Date:830214 (Container 43, Folder 9)
  Memo "Inquiry Prior to Initial Investments"
- PacketCable & Tech Date:830317 (Container 43, Folder 10)
  Stock Purchase Agreement
- PacketCable & Tech Date:830324 (Container 43, Folder 11)
  Letter to Terry Tims, Standard Oil, re: discussion during the week
- PacketCable & Tech Date:830325 (Container 43, Folder 12)
  Standard Oil's second draft of the Stock Purchase Agreement
- PacketCable & Tech Date:830414 (Container 43, Folder 13)
  Stock Purchase Agreement, 280,000 Shares of Common Stock
- PacketCable & Tech Date:830420 (Container 43, Folder 14)
  Agenda for April 25, 1983 meeting
- PacketCable & Tech Date:830517 (Container 43, Folder 15)
  Market research report from International Resource Development on Teleshopping
- PacketCable & Tech Date:831229 (Container 43, Folder 16)
  FASB draft on accounting treatment of junior stock plans
- PacketCable & Tech Date:840127 (Container 43, Folder 17)
  Resolution requiring unanimous written consent of the Board of Directors
- PacketCable & Tech Date:840130 (Container 43, Folder 18)
  Diagram (hand-drawn) showing Standard's Rights
- PacketCable & Tech Date:840203 (Container 43, Folder 19)
  Stock Purchase Agreement, Feb. 3, 1984
- PacketCable & Tech Date:840401 (Container 43, Folder 20)
  Stock ownership list (stock analysis)
- PacketCable & Tech Date:840814 (Container 43, Folder 21)
  To Standard Oil from Fenwick, Stone, Davis & West, draft of Amended & Restated Articles of incorporation
- PacketCable & Tech Date:840221 (Container 43, Folder 22)
  Written Consent of Board of Directors, adopted as of Feb. 17, 1984
- PacketCable & Tech Date:840705 (Container 43, Folder 23)
  CDA Merger Hearing and Shareholders Meeting
- PacketCable & Tech Date:840723 (Container 43, Folder 24)
  Script for 1984 Special Shareholders' Meeting, July 23, 1984
- PacketCable & Tech Date:850913 (Container 43, Folder 25)
  Board of Directors Meeting, Sept. 13, 1985
- PacketCable & Tech Date:851003 (Container 43, Folder 26)
  List of shareholders (hand-written) who signed written consent
- PacketCable & Tech Date:851108 (Container 43, Folder 27)
  Board of Directors Meeting, Nov. 8, 1985
- PacketCable & Tech Date:851213 (Container 43, Folder 28)
  Notice of Special Board Meeting, Dec. 13, 1985
- PacketCable & Tech Date:860108 (Container 43, Folder 29)
  Notice of Special Board Meeting, Jan. 8, 1986
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:840227 (Container 45, Folder 1)
  Moving Expenses, Steve Millard
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:851206 (Container 45, Folder 8)
  PacketCable areas of commonality with ATT Technologies
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:850924 (Container 45, Folder 2)
  Lehman Brothers Exit
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:850928 (Container 45, Folder 3)
  World Business, "Amoco: The Tortoise Wins Again"
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:851001 (Container 45, Folder 4)
  Discussion with Marc Schweig, AT&T
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:851101 (Container 45, Folder 5)
  Hand-written notes from Steve C. re: AT&T
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:851105 (Container 45, Folder 6)
  PB & Steve Millard's move to 50% time
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:851105 (Container 45, Folder 7)
  Copy of documents filed by Amoco in US Patent Office (Townsend & Townsend)
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:851218 (Container 45, Folder 9)
  Steve Campbell's memo on meetings the week of Dec. 16, 1985
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:851231 (Container 45, Folder 10)
  Packet Technologies/PacketDax Spinout
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:860104 (Container 45, Folder 11)
  Preincorporation Agreement
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:860105 (Container 45, Folder 12)
  Compensation of David Robertson
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:860124 (Container 45, Folder 13)
  Draft of Asset Purchase Agreement whereby Xadtekcap will purchase certain assets from Packet
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:860207 (Container 45, Folder 14)
  Stock and Warrant Purchase Agreement
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:860307 (Container 45, Folder 15)
  Stratacom Closing Party
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:860328 (Container 45, Folder 16)
  IPX Integrated Packet Exchange: A Third Generation T-carrier Network Management System
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:860714 (Container 45, Folder 17)
  Stratacom Clippings
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:860908 (Container 45, Folder 18)
  Sale of Stock
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:860909 (Container 45, Folder 19)
  Packet Board Meeting, Sept. 9, 1986
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:861216 (Container 45, Folder 20)
  Telephone Board Meeting Scheduled for Friday, Dec. 19, 1986
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:870128 (Container 45, Folder 21)
  Kriens letter to PB regarding observations from Zraket regarding StrataCom's Integrated Packet Exchange
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:870508 (Container 45, Folder 22)
  Amoco and Small Companies (new strategy)
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:880101 (Container 45, Folder 23)
  Executive Summary (creation of NEWCO)
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:881107 (Container 45, Folder 24)
  Amoco "screwing" (Packet's write-offs)
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:890104 (Container 45, Folder 25)
  PB's letter to Tobkin re: Stratacom & Packet Technologies (stock distribution)
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:890119 (Container 45, Folder 26)
  PN's letter to Liepold re: Packet Technologies (letter to come from Robertson)
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:890501 (Container 45, Folder 27)
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:900201 (Container 45, Folder 28)
  Stratacom Brochures
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:910514 (Container 45, Folder 29)
  Notice of Annual Meeting, May 14, 1991
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:920101 (Container 45, Folder 30)
  The IPX Product Family
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:920401 (Container 45, Folder 31)
  Brochure, "A Distributed automatic cross-connect system with new packet technology for enhanced use of DS1 facilities
- Stratacom/PacTech Date:920515 (Container 45, Folder 32)